<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Fantasy - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Fantasy - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1701-avengers-endgame.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1701-avengers-endgame.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The plot of the movie "Avengers: Endgame" tells about the events after Thanos was able to carry out his plan. Half Vmelennoj evaporate and now nobody knows what will happen next. Naturally the situation is not the best way, and many have lost their loved ones. Stark is committed in another world and no one knows if he is alive. The same is happening on the ground is a real mess. Many people do not believe that someday will be able to fix something, but do it. The Avengers lost their war and it seems that there is no way out of the situation. But give up they are just not going. Will have to challenge the mad Titan and try to win this time. To do so would be extremely difficult and complicated, but it is to rely on the positive result. Only by bringing all his forces together, they will be able to strike, which would probably fix this whole situation. Ahead of their final battle, in which each character would try to participate. What this all will end and whether they will oppose such a strong enemy? Once failed, so it is not known why this all will lead! War is only just beginning and is nearing the most finals, which will put an end to this confrontation.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Fantasy  Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 17:12:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Wolves</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[One day, waking up at night, the protagonist finds his murdered parents. Having decided that it was his handiwork, the guy turns into a wild Wolf and leaves home. The true reason for leaving the hero from home-an unfair accusation Caleb murder their own parents. He did not commit, however, forced to hide in a safe place in town called Wolf Ridge. As it turns out, this place is filled with mysticism and is inextricably linked to the secret family guy by Caleb will have to unravel. The life of a young man no longer will be the same, because the entire responsibility he learns his true purpose in life.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Action   Fantasy   Horror   Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:57:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Hellboy</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1865-hellboy.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1865-hellboy.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Powerful and insane Nimue, enlightening centuries later, intends to arrange the Apocalypse and plunge mankind into chaos. The hero of the movie to fight the hordes of evil, which called itself the Queen for help. Sometimes it seems that the guy can't do this an impossible mission. The girl turns out to be the wife of the great Wizard Merlin. Of course, fight alone with this enemy cannot and battle with evil our Sapphire will assist a team of people, each of whom is a professional.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Action    Fantasy    Horror    Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 09:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Shazam!</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1862-shazam.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1862-shazam.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The old sorcerer is no longer able to fight the forces of evil. It is time to find a successor. The magician's choice fell on 14-year-old Billy Bjetsona. All that is required from the teen-speak the name of the ancient Mage-Shazam and the guy immediately turns into a superhero, with adult. From new abilities the guy Boggle. Together with her best friend and then they test new skills, which are not so easy to cope. But after meeting with mighty villain Dr. Taddeusom Sivanoj Billy realizes that was endowed with superpowers is not accidental. He has to save the world from evil.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Action     Comedy     Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 14:04:41 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Dumbo</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1861-dumbo.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1861-dumbo.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Marc de Medici is a famous circus impresario. Once he had appointed the former circus star Holt Fjerriera and his children, Millie and Joe guardians newborn slonjonka named Dumbo. This baby elephant is incredibly large ears, which immediately became the subject of constant jokes by colleagues Holt.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Adventure      Family      Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:36:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Smallfoot</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["Smallfoot" overturns the myth of bigfutah upside down. In it a young resourceful Yeti is faced with the fact that his deep conviction that there is no man. News on "smolfute" brought him fame and a chance to win the girl of his dreams. And yet-cause a stir among ordinary Yeti who now wonder what else lives in the big world outside their small snowbound villages.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Animation       Comedy       Family       Fantasy       Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 11:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Voldemort: Origins of the Heir</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1825-voldemort-origins-of-the-heir.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1825-voldemort-origins-of-the-heir.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie tells about youth of Voldemort, the strong dark magician from Potteriana, and about how contemporaries recognized him and began to be afraid to say his name. Besides Voldemort, in the movie also his classmates from other faculties of Hogwarts appear. In the center of a plot there is a series of mysterious murders which are investigated by the magician Grisha Maklagen.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Adventure        Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:50:27 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Suicide Squad: Hell to Pay</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1820-suicide-squad-hell-to-pay.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1820-suicide-squad-hell-to-pay.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Amanda Waller brings together the Task Force of Ickx consisting of Dedshot, Harley Quinn, the Captain Bumeranga, the Murderer of Moroz, the Brazen Serpent and the Bronze Tiger again. Their task — to find Steel Maksum and to receive for Amanda the mystical black playing card with the inscription "Free Exit from Hell".]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Action         Animation         Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:31:18 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Apocalypse Rising</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1792-apocalypse-rising.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1792-apocalypse-rising.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[For the morning after the noisy party Sam finds out that its former, her new boyfriend and in general all turned into the zombie around. And the only place to all Paris where he can feel safe, is an apartment where he woke up. What to do? To run or remain? To be protected or attack most?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Comedy          Fantasy          Horror          Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 21:03:40 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Sherlock Gnomes</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Gnomeo and Juliette are waited by a new fascinating adventure — now in huge London. When heroes with families and friends move to the city, their main care — to prepare the new garden by spring. But soon they learn disturbing news: across all London their fellows gnomes enigmatically disappear! And once Gnomeo and Juliette, having come back home, find, as all their relatives disappeared. In such situation can only come to the rescue … Sherlock Gnoms. The famous detective becomes on protection of inhabitants of the London gardens and not without the aid of the faithful companion Watson undertakes to solve tangled case.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Animation           Comedy           Family           Fantasy           Mystery           Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>