<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Family - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Family - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>The Monkey King</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1892-the-monkey-king.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1892-the-monkey-king.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["The Monkey King" is based on ancient Chinese mythology, according to which Buddhism appeared according to this legend. The story in the film will be about the popular character of Chinese youth and in children's literature the monkey King. His personality is complex and contradictory: playful and sad, heroic and comic. The film tells the story of three worlds (demons, people and heaven). In immemorial times, demons, who decided to seize the sky, lost in combat and were is banished. The heavens suffered with a view to their recovery one of the gods sacrificed himself. To archaeologist nick Orton, during an expedition to China, was the goddess Kwan Yin with a request. The fate of the whole world is at stake. You want to find an ancient monuscript, which was stolen by demons and rescue from captivity monkey King, who is in prison for five hundred years. San Wukong (the monkey king) was born from drops of tears of the goddess who saved the Sky. Temptations began to Eclipse his soul, he learns his strength and destroys the castle in which he was born. For this he was punished by the Gods and sent to prison.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Family]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:05:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Dumbo</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1861-dumbo.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1861-dumbo.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Marc de Medici is a famous circus impresario. Once he had appointed the former circus star Holt Fjerriera and his children, Millie and Joe guardians newborn slonjonka named Dumbo. This baby elephant is incredibly large ears, which immediately became the subject of constant jokes by colleagues Holt.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Adventure   Family   Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:36:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Pokémon Detective Pikachu</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Action movie occur in the huge metropolis Reim-city, where people live close to Pokemon. Tim is a guy who's dreamt to become a trainer Pokemon. His father Harry is a real legend of the police station, which was the best detective. Man mysteriously disappeared and nobody can find it. Tim really wants to find it, but realizes that most cope with such a complex task will be incredibly difficult. But one night, he encounters a pretty-type Pokémon, Pikachu, who calls himself supersyshhikom. It offers its assistance and the guy claims that they are bound to find Harry.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Action    Comedy    Family    Mystery    Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:48:23 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Smallfoot</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["Smallfoot" overturns the myth of bigfutah upside down. In it a young resourceful Yeti is faced with the fact that his deep conviction that there is no man. News on "smolfute" brought him fame and a chance to win the girl of his dreams. And yet-cause a stir among ordinary Yeti who now wonder what else lives in the big world outside their small snowbound villages.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Animation     Comedy     Family     Fantasy     Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 11:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Lego DC Super Hero Girls: Super-Villain High</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1851-lego-dc-super-hero-girls-super-villain-high.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1851-lego-dc-super-hero-girls-super-villain-high.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[After near School of Superheroes the new school opens, supergirls find themselves in the face of new threat. Now to the Wonderful Female, Supergirls, Bat girls and other it is necessary not only to worry for the estimates, but also for safety of the friends and relatives, and also all residents. Supergirls should fight this time with School of Supervillains!]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Adventure      Action      Animation      Comedy      Family      Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:20:40 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Paws P.I.</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1848-paws-pi.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1848-paws-pi.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Petter is a typical teenager, it is betrayed loving the father and mother. His father was the owner of the detective agency until recently. Soon the agency went bankrupt and it had to be closed. St. Petersburg family suffered serious financial losses. The son sharply endured defeat of the father. The man hard was given the decision to close the agency, but an exit was not. It is sensitive having sat and having thought, Peter finds the solution how to help the father. He wants to restore the detective agency. Understanding that alone he will hardly manage to cope, the boy takes in assistants to a faithful doggie and parrot who as it became clear later, are able to talk. After a while friends get to epicenter of serious opposition with the most dangerous person in the city.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Family]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:12:33 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Monsters at Large</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1846-monsters-at-large.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1846-monsters-at-large.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The main character of the movie – the young guy who is called Alex. Now he very much worries about the younger brother as that dreams nightmares for a long time and fears and quite strange imaginations do not allow to live. All the matter is that he often sees monsters and therefore is afraid of a shadow. Parents, as well as Alex, perfectly understand that children at such age often think out something, dream and then trust in it. Therefore they cannot help the defenseless child in any way, and refuse to recognize their existence at all. All this causes suspicion in Alex, and he decides to correct independently this situation and to find some way out. Together with the company of friends they begin hunting for these monsters and do it in playful way. And everything was good until children did not meet the real monster and now their game accepts absolutely other turns.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Family]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:07:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Grandpa&#039;s Great Escape</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1824-grandpas-great-escape.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1824-grandpas-great-escape.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Three generations are forced to live under a roof of one house. The head of the family suffers from Alzheimer's disease that forces it to remember the past when he was a professional pilot of the fighter. The grandson Jack supports tricks of the grandfather who climbs up every evening a roof of the family mansion, imagining himself at Spitfayr's steering wheel. Parents of the boy do not share his enthusiasm, and are going to send the grandfather to nursing home what the young man furiously opposes to. What will difficult family opposition end with?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Family]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:45:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Brimming with Love</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1812-brimming-with-love.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1812-brimming-with-love.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The owner of small cafe is a good judge of how to help people to find couple. He considers that he is a professional in this case, does not face yet the journalist whose heart it is difficult to melt.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Family          Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 11:59:57 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Sherlock Gnomes</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Gnomeo and Juliette are waited by a new fascinating adventure — now in huge London. When heroes with families and friends move to the city, their main care — to prepare the new garden by spring. But soon they learn disturbing news: across all London their fellows gnomes enigmatically disappear! And once Gnomeo and Juliette, having come back home, find, as all their relatives disappeared. In such situation can only come to the rescue … Sherlock Gnoms. The famous detective becomes on protection of inhabitants of the London gardens and not without the aid of the faithful companion Watson undertakes to solve tangled case.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Animation           Comedy           Family           Fantasy           Mystery           Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>