<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Romance - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Romance - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Shaadi Ke Side Effects</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Comic tape "Shaadi Ke Side Effects" directed by Saket chaudhari. The slogan of the family film was a simple question and answer: "Boring to live? Have a baby." The film is about a typical family problems. The story of Sid – the hero-lover and trish – a modern girl who got married and waiting for the baby. When the baby was born, the young family added a lot of everyday problems. In various situations, marriage is tested for strength. The modern attitude towards family values - fine disclosed Saket Chaudhary in the film. The ease of the tape gives music, dancing and bright costumes that are inherent in all Indian films.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Comedy  Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:28:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Love Is Strange</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1874-love-is-strange.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1874-love-is-strange.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The story is about a same-sex couple, Ben and George, who lived together for 39 years and eventually officially registered their marriage at the Manhattan city hall. However, after returning from their honeymoon, they receive unpleasant news: Ben, who worked as a choir conductor in a Catholic school, decided to fire. Having no more opportunity to pay for the small apartment, "newlyweds" are compelled to settle separately from each other. One of them moves to his nephew and his family in Brooklyn, and the other - in the next apartment, where they live two gay police officers.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Drama   Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:00:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Sweetest Heart</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1850-the-sweetest-heart.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1850-the-sweetest-heart.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[To the owner of cafe and the confectioner Maddie the attractive banker helps to save her business. But their potential novel becomes complicated when the first love of Maddie — Nate unexpectedly comes back to the city.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:18:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Lady Macbeth</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1819-lady-macbeth.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1819-lady-macbeth.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Victorian England of the 19th century. The small village living according to the special ways and customs inherent in that time. The young girl by the name of Catherine becomes the spouse of the man who is twice more senior than her. The newly made family treats Catherine with neglect and lets the girl know that to wait for care and love in this house is not necessary to it. After a while Catherine strikes up acquaintance to the young worker of a farm of the spouse, and between them the passion flashes.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Drama     Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:29:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Competition</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1818-the-competition.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1818-the-competition.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The main character, following the "theory of a pig", finishes any relations after 6 months to avoid treason. But once she meets the man who wishes to refute this theory.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Comedy      Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:19:10 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Middleground</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1815-middleground.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1815-middleground.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Did you sometime think that it could be died in a different way? You could be born in other place, make other choice, go on an unfamiliar way …<br><br>He and she as if stiffened in a routine of similar days where dreams seem more real, than series of everyday life. But what if the parallel world at all not illusion and once someone from them plunges into it as in real?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Drama       Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:08:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Brimming with Love</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1812-brimming-with-love.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1812-brimming-with-love.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The owner of small cafe is a good judge of how to help people to find couple. He considers that he is a professional in this case, does not face yet the journalist whose heart it is difficult to melt.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Family        Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 11:59:57 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Cooking with Love</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1790-cooking-with-love.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1790-cooking-with-love.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The hardworking and optimistic teleprodyusersha of Kelly has no time for love. Together with the tutor Amanda she plunges into a new season of the show "Small Gourmet" when the hot chef who replaced the permanent leader rushes into her life. In fight for success of a show, they understand that at them much in common: love to food, to children that participate in a show, and to each other.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Comedy         Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 21:00:13 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Sherlock Gnomes</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1789-sherlock-gnomes.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Gnomeo and Juliette are waited by a new fascinating adventure — now in huge London. When heroes with families and friends move to the city, their main care — to prepare the new garden by spring. But soon they learn disturbing news: across all London their fellows gnomes enigmatically disappear! And once Gnomeo and Juliette, having come back home, find, as all their relatives disappeared. In such situation can only come to the rescue … Sherlock Gnoms. The famous detective becomes on protection of inhabitants of the London gardens and not without the aid of the faithful companion Watson undertakes to solve tangled case.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Adventure          Animation          Comedy          Family          Fantasy          Mystery          Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:57:46 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Titan</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1787-the-titan.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1787-the-titan.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The American military Rick takes part in the grandiose space program. The best minds of the planet try to create superpeople who after death of Earth will provide continuation of existence of mankind on the planet the Titan. However the experiment with genes leads to absolutely unpredictable consequences.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Drama           Mystery           Romance           Sci-Fi           Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 20:52:17 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>