<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Comedy - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Comedy - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1897-guardians-of-the-galaxy.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1897-guardians-of-the-galaxy.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[While still a child, the protagonist Peter Quill becomes a victim of kidnapping by extraterrestrials. As an adult, he takes the nickname Star Lord and turns into one of the most legendary bandits throughout the Galaxy, but, at least, he thinks so. Once Peter in SED mysterious and very powerful artifact, owned by the powerful and knowledgeable not pity villain Ronan, who yearns to capture the universe. However, there are still others who wants the artifact, resulting in Peter turns out to be a victim of intergalactic hunting. Ahead of his many breathtaking adventure, meeting new friends, with whom they have to work together to save the Galaxy.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Comedy  Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Force Majeure</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the center of the plot of the dramatic painting "Force Majeure" young couple from Sweden Thomas and Abby, who together with their two children goes to rest in the French Alps. They are waiting for a wonderful hotel, the majestic nature of the mountains, and a lot of unforgettable entertainment. It would seem that nothing can spoil their family vacation. However, fate had slightly different plans, and on the second day of stay at the ski resort there is an event that threatens the marriage of Thomas and Abby.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Comedy   Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:06:53 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Shaadi Ke Side Effects</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Comic tape "Shaadi Ke Side Effects" directed by Saket chaudhari. The slogan of the family film was a simple question and answer: "Boring to live? Have a baby." The film is about a typical family problems. The story of Sid – the hero-lover and trish – a modern girl who got married and waiting for the baby. When the baby was born, the young family added a lot of everyday problems. In various situations, marriage is tested for strength. The modern attitude towards family values - fine disclosed Saket Chaudhary in the film. The ease of the tape gives music, dancing and bright costumes that are inherent in all Indian films.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Comedy    Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:28:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>What We Do in the Shadows</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The film tells the story of the life of three neighbors in the apartment: silent and strict Vladislav, mannered Viagra and extremely active Deacon. They are immortal vampires and try to adapt to the modern conditions of life in the small town of Wellington. Earlier the main problem all the vampires were killing the light of the sun and not uragement in any mirrors. So survival was more or less real. And even outlive many of the annoying hunters. But now other times have come, and everything has changed dramatically. The unfortunate trio is not so easy to adapt, because they are haunted by exorbitant rent, ubiquitous sunlight and who knows who invented face control in bars and clubs. In addition, there are a lot of other various troubles: from annoying hospitable residents in the neighborhood to daily washing dishes...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Comedy     Horror]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:59 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bermuda Tentacles</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[American Fantasy horror film (Bermuda Tentacles) can find a response in the soul of even the most sophisticated cinephile. The action unfolds on kinoistorii sea Bermuda triangle. Peaceful ship quietly goes to the coveted military objective-to shore. But it is precisely at the moment of calm and serenity in the way the vessel is raised sea monster is bulky, the stench of foul, heartbreaking. And then ship the AIR FORCE will have to maintain an unequal battle with the sea giant. All possible forces and guns. Bermuda tentacles leave no choice: fight or die.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Adventure      Action      Comedy      Horror      Sci-Fi      Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:08 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bang Bang</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1879-bang-bang.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1879-bang-bang.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the blockbuster "Bang Bang", you'll see an exciting narrative about a girl Harlin Sahni. She is an employee of the Bank, the dreamer who can love and be sexy. This girl is pure and innocent and at the same time. She accidentally meets an attractive and full of mystery Radzhivira Rand. It is open, risky and attractive. And he immediately falls into the soul of the girl. This meeting leads to an exciting adventure. Harlin learns that Radzhivir former spy trying to clear his name, but it turns out he is not very good. Explosions, shootouts, chases and complete chaos. That's what happens to make Radzhiviru. But, despite all this Bedlam and chaos, he leaves to convince Harlin in that he is not a bad guy. But whether Harlin trust him? And is it worth it? And how can he reclaim his name? Though the film is a thriller, but at the same time, full of love, romance and passion. Also in the movie there are a lot of comedy and humor. Captivating storyline intrigue until the end, holding the film. All of the above and good actors is, just what you're looking for a good movie]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Action       Comedy       Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:25:03 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Drive Hard</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1877-drive-hard.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1877-drive-hard.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the not-too-distant past, the character of John Cusack professional motor racing, but as time passed, the former glory and now the man is forced to go to rest. Peter got a driving instructor, allowing you to indulge in a favorite activity, while not risking their lives at enormous speeds. True, if the fate of plans to bring in a person's life the next test of fortitude, you no names of upcoming events.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Action        Comedy        Crime]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:22:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Hector and the Search for Happiness</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1868-hector-and-the-search-for-happiness.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1868-hector-and-the-search-for-happiness.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Obajatelnomu psychiatrist, leading his practice in London, had a chance to become a main character in the film Journey in search of happiness Hector (Hector and the Search for Happiness). Anyone have once disappointed from their chosen profession. Some find the strength to make "mistakes" and begin to work more efficiently. Other-launch a process "of searching yourself and your place in this world". Hector sincerely strove to make their clients happier, give them genuine joy each day. Gradually realized the futility of attempts, and the understanding that his own life is no different from the stories of patients. It's time to drop everything and find out whether there is happiness at all?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Adventure         Comedy         Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:51:23 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Shazam!</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1862-shazam.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1862-shazam.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The old sorcerer is no longer able to fight the forces of evil. It is time to find a successor. The magician's choice fell on 14-year-old Billy Bjetsona. All that is required from the teen-speak the name of the ancient Mage-Shazam and the guy immediately turns into a superhero, with adult. From new abilities the guy Boggle. Together with her best friend and then they test new skills, which are not so easy to cope. But after meeting with mighty villain Dr. Taddeusom Sivanoj Billy realizes that was endowed with superpowers is not accidental. He has to save the world from evil.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Adventure          Action          Comedy          Fantasy]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 14:04:41 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Pokémon Detective Pikachu</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Action movie occur in the huge metropolis Reim-city, where people live close to Pokemon. Tim is a guy who's dreamt to become a trainer Pokemon. His father Harry is a real legend of the police station, which was the best detective. Man mysteriously disappeared and nobody can find it. Tim really wants to find it, but realizes that most cope with such a complex task will be incredibly difficult. But one night, he encounters a pretty-type Pokémon, Pikachu, who calls himself supersyshhikom. It offers its assistance and the guy claims that they are bound to find Harry.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Action           Comedy           Family           Mystery           Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:48:23 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>