<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Boyhood</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1895-boyhood.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1895-boyhood.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Drama "Boyhood" film is a masterpiece, experiment. Twelve-year project shows the audience a person growing up from young boy to adult young men. Director Richard Linklater was able to show and convey through film the feelings of a little boy, his emotions. The story of a typical American family and their child, the boy's experiences of divorce mom and dad, problems with classmates, UPS and downs, the first kiss and the first feelings. The film-memoirs of the life of the generations, cutting fragments, which evoke nostalgia and touches on the most touching moments in life. "Adolescence" is shot without embellishment, without bright grim and editing, life is what it is. Watching first the baby, his relatives, the viewer will live their lives and in the end in this boy everyone will see himself, no one will remain indifferent. The film fascinates with its reality, simplicity, but with such a strong background and for a long time will remain in the hearts of the original, light, varied music that accompanies the film gives special colors to this film.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:09:27 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>As the Gods Will</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The action of the action-movie "As the Gods Will" takes place in our days in Japan. A teenager named sun Takahata is studying in high school, and unlike his peers, he is not quite happy with his life, because it seems to him boring and monotonous. The guy dreams that something extraordinary and memorable happened. And once the desire Suna implemented, but not as he had imagined. The school begins to appear strange live toys that offer students to play a variety of games. At first glance, everything looks harmless, but in reality it is not so simple. Toys, which is headed by the ancient God the Dolls are actually do not leave children, since those who refused to play, the result will meet the same fate as the loser certain death. Those who still manage to win, will be given life. Here is only will whether such?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Horror   Sci-Fi   Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Force Majeure</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the center of the plot of the dramatic painting "Force Majeure" young couple from Sweden Thomas and Abby, who together with their two children goes to rest in the French Alps. They are waiting for a wonderful hotel, the majestic nature of the mountains, and a lot of unforgettable entertainment. It would seem that nothing can spoil their family vacation. However, fate had slightly different plans, and on the second day of stay at the ski resort there is an event that threatens the marriage of Thomas and Abby.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Comedy    Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:06:53 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>One on One</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Oh-Hyun is a young guy who is a hired killer, working for an influential criminal group. He always brings the case to the end and never being torments of conscience, because for him it's just a job. The next order of his boss, who always pays good money, he becomes a murder of a young schoolgirl, and o-Hyung as always impeccably performs its work. However, he then falls into the hands of unknown to him, dressed in military uniforms, who begin to torture him, trying to learn the name of those who ordered the girl. In addition to on-Hena under suspicion to fall a few more people, and violent the Avengers will not rest until each and every one of them will be punished.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Crime     Drama     Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>We Are Young. We Are Strong.</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Rostock in August 1992 year. The situation in the port city, which after the fall of the Berlin wall is not the best of times and suffers from massive unemployment, is heating up with every second. All dissatisfaction with radical residents refer to "home with sunflowers" — giant building, which houses a youth hostel and a camp for Vietnamese seeking asylum in Germany as refugees. The film traces the story of three Heroes: a young Vietnamese Lin, dreaming of a better future, young Stephen, which falls into the company of neo-Nazis, and his father, Martin-local politics-Democrat trying to maneuver between the need to carry responsibility for what is happening and the desire to preserve reputation.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Crime      Drama      History]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:00:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Interstellar</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1888-interstellar.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1888-interstellar.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie "Interstellar" occurs in the near future. The climate on Earth has changed significantly, and the high concentration of nitrogen will soon lead to loss of life. There is an urgent need to look for another planet to move on it the entire human race. Scientists have discovered a wormhole in space through which you can move to another Galaxy. This is the only way for the salvation of all mankind.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Drama       Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:58:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Shaadi Ke Side Effects</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1883-shaadi-ke-side-effects.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Comic tape "Shaadi Ke Side Effects" directed by Saket chaudhari. The slogan of the family film was a simple question and answer: "Boring to live? Have a baby." The film is about a typical family problems. The story of Sid – the hero-lover and trish – a modern girl who got married and waiting for the baby. When the baby was born, the young family added a lot of everyday problems. In various situations, marriage is tested for strength. The modern attitude towards family values - fine disclosed Saket Chaudhary in the film. The ease of the tape gives music, dancing and bright costumes that are inherent in all Indian films.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Comedy        Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:28:56 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>What We Do in the Shadows</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The film tells the story of the life of three neighbors in the apartment: silent and strict Vladislav, mannered Viagra and extremely active Deacon. They are immortal vampires and try to adapt to the modern conditions of life in the small town of Wellington. Earlier the main problem all the vampires were killing the light of the sun and not uragement in any mirrors. So survival was more or less real. And even outlive many of the annoying hunters. But now other times have come, and everything has changed dramatically. The unfortunate trio is not so easy to adapt, because they are haunted by exorbitant rent, ubiquitous sunlight and who knows who invented face control in bars and clubs. In addition, there are a lot of other various troubles: from annoying hospitable residents in the neighborhood to daily washing dishes...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Comedy         Horror]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:59 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Deepsea Challenge 3D</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1878-deepsea-challenge-3d.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1878-deepsea-challenge-3d.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[James Cameron's more attracted to the idea of shooting a documentary. One of such works and is "Deepsea Challenge 3D". For 90 minutes the viewer presents captivating views and beauty of one of the mysteries of the planet. This is Maria trough. 3D viewer watching descent camera. The beauty of the environment around, new life. All this Director tried to show in their work. He tries to show the viewer in your video all the love and passion that he feels for the discovery and suspense. Plunging deeper and deeper into the capsule Cameron step by step, describes his actions on how it all began, as specialists have created a Special Chamber for diving. And what puzzles keeps our planet Earth.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:23:58 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>About Alex</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1876-about-alex.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1876-about-alex.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The originality of the plot of the drama "About Alex", paradoxically it sounds, is its banality. A few friends grew up, did different things, began to see each other rarely.But as the saying goes, a friend in need is a friend indeed. Seven friends unite again to solve a difficult life situation of one of them. Alex undertakes attempt to suicide, that and collects friends again. However, after common joyful memories, old grievances and misunderstandings emerge. Seeming strong friendship begins to crumble like a house of cards.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:02:41 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>