<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Drama - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Drama - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Boyhood</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1895-boyhood.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1895-boyhood.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Drama "Boyhood" film is a masterpiece, experiment. Twelve-year project shows the audience a person growing up from young boy to adult young men. Director Richard Linklater was able to show and convey through film the feelings of a little boy, his emotions. The story of a typical American family and their child, the boy's experiences of divorce mom and dad, problems with classmates, UPS and downs, the first kiss and the first feelings. The film-memoirs of the life of the generations, cutting fragments, which evoke nostalgia and touches on the most touching moments in life. "Adolescence" is shot without embellishment, without bright grim and editing, life is what it is. Watching first the baby, his relatives, the viewer will live their lives and in the end in this boy everyone will see himself, no one will remain indifferent. The film fascinates with its reality, simplicity, but with such a strong background and for a long time will remain in the hearts of the original, light, varied music that accompanies the film gives special colors to this film.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:09:27 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Force Majeure</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1893-force-majeure.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the center of the plot of the dramatic painting "Force Majeure" young couple from Sweden Thomas and Abby, who together with their two children goes to rest in the French Alps. They are waiting for a wonderful hotel, the majestic nature of the mountains, and a lot of unforgettable entertainment. It would seem that nothing can spoil their family vacation. However, fate had slightly different plans, and on the second day of stay at the ski resort there is an event that threatens the marriage of Thomas and Abby.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Comedy   Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:06:53 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>One on One</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Oh-Hyun is a young guy who is a hired killer, working for an influential criminal group. He always brings the case to the end and never being torments of conscience, because for him it's just a job. The next order of his boss, who always pays good money, he becomes a murder of a young schoolgirl, and o-Hyung as always impeccably performs its work. However, he then falls into the hands of unknown to him, dressed in military uniforms, who begin to torture him, trying to learn the name of those who ordered the girl. In addition to on-Hena under suspicion to fall a few more people, and violent the Avengers will not rest until each and every one of them will be punished.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Crime    Drama    Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>We Are Young. We Are Strong.</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Rostock in August 1992 year. The situation in the port city, which after the fall of the Berlin wall is not the best of times and suffers from massive unemployment, is heating up with every second. All dissatisfaction with radical residents refer to "home with sunflowers" — giant building, which houses a youth hostel and a camp for Vietnamese seeking asylum in Germany as refugees. The film traces the story of three Heroes: a young Vietnamese Lin, dreaming of a better future, young Stephen, which falls into the company of neo-Nazis, and his father, Martin-local politics-Democrat trying to maneuver between the need to carry responsibility for what is happening and the desire to preserve reputation.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Crime     Drama     History]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:00:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Interstellar</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1888-interstellar.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1888-interstellar.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie "Interstellar" occurs in the near future. The climate on Earth has changed significantly, and the high concentration of nitrogen will soon lead to loss of life. There is an urgent need to look for another planet to move on it the entire human race. Scientists have discovered a wormhole in space through which you can move to another Galaxy. This is the only way for the salvation of all mankind.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Adventure      Drama      Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:58:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Ek Villain</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Guru-ruthless and cruel, the machine working on the political system. In his life, he committed the unimaginable things that now do not give him peace. It is in crisis, from which no exit-anyway, he does not see. Insomnia is a common State for the hero. Meditations on morality increasingly annoys him.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Action       Crime       Drama       Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:57:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Fatal Encounter</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1885-the-fatal-encounter.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1885-the-fatal-encounter.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The story of conspiracy and murder, about the fate of those who are destined to live or die, be saved or be faithful. The plot expands around the life of King Jeongjo of Joseon in the Joseon era.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Action        Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 20:28:47 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>About Alex</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1876-about-alex.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1876-about-alex.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The originality of the plot of the drama "About Alex", paradoxically it sounds, is its banality. A few friends grew up, did different things, began to see each other rarely.But as the saying goes, a friend in need is a friend indeed. Seven friends unite again to solve a difficult life situation of one of them. Alex undertakes attempt to suicide, that and collects friends again. However, after common joyful memories, old grievances and misunderstandings emerge. Seeming strong friendship begins to crumble like a house of cards.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:02:41 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Manglehorn</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1875-manglehorn.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1875-manglehorn.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the center of the plot of the art drama "Manglehorn" an elderly man named AJ Manglehorn. He lives in a small provincial town, and leads an unremarkable lifestyle. AJ owns a small workshop for making keys and repairing locks. His services are constantly in demand, because accidentally slammed the door of the house or car is not uncommon, and everything else, he is a true professional. But none of the clients even realize what a turbulent past he has behind him. Once upon a time, Manglehorn was a fairly well-known safecracker in criminal circles, who could open any lock. But once in his life there was a girl who forced the hero not only to think about his life, but also faced a difficult choice…]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:01:31 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Love Is Strange</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1874-love-is-strange.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1874-love-is-strange.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The story is about a same-sex couple, Ben and George, who lived together for 39 years and eventually officially registered their marriage at the Manhattan city hall. However, after returning from their honeymoon, they receive unpleasant news: Ben, who worked as a choir conductor in a Catholic school, decided to fire. Having no more opportunity to pay for the small apartment, "newlyweds" are compelled to settle separately from each other. One of them moves to his nephew and his family in Brooklyn, and the other - in the next apartment, where they live two gay police officers.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Drama           Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 10:00:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>