<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Music - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Music - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Florence Foster Jenkins</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/964-florence-foster-jenkins-v4.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/964-florence-foster-jenkins-v4.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Florence Foster Jenkins always dreamed to sing on the stage. Here only the nature did not allocate it with hearing and voice. But unless the lack of talent is an obstacle for the person who very much seeks for execution of a dream? And the rank of the most useless singer in the world not all can spoil mood!]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Comedy  Biography  Drama  Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 18:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Hail, Caesar!</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/975-hail-caesar.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/975-hail-caesar.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Welcome to Hollywood – the empire of gloss, luxury and defect. Here idols of millions live. That day – a feast for society columnists. And once the leading man in the movie "Long Live Caesar!" disappears. Neither the wife, nor numerous mistresses know where it. And now the producer of studio is waited by cheerful day, it has to find a star before reporters …]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Comedy   Drama   Music   Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 09:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Leap!</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/927-leap.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/927-leap.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Events will be developed around the little orphan who, following a dream to become the ballerina, comes to Paris in 1879.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Animation    Comedy    Family    Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 14:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Popstar: Never Stop Never Stopping</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1038-popstar-never-stop-never-stopping-v2.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1038-popstar-never-stop-never-stopping-v2.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Since the childhood Conner was crazy about music. Still the child he with two best friends created The Style Boyz group. The group became very popular, and Connor zazvezditsya, having decided that success of group - only his merit. One childhood friend ceased to talk to him at all, another works for Conner as the DJ. And the best friends of the superstar - his manager, the organizer of parties and other unclear persons to whom only to hang out from morning to the night. And here great day - an exit of a new solo album comes. But, as we know, the above you flew up, the more painfully will fall.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Comedy     Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 09:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Sing Street</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1047-sing-street.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1047-sing-street.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The nostalgic musical drama about growing. When the economic crisis of the 1980th strikes Conor's family, it is transferred from prestigious private school to state. The teenager faces roughness and ignorance of the new environment and, besides, falls in love with the inaccessible beauty. Wishing to impress the girl, Conor brings together rock group.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Comedy      Drama      Music      Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 08:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>La La Land</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/998-la-la-land.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/998-la-la-land.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[It is a love story of the starlet which between listenings serves coffee to the taken place movie stars, and the fanatical jazz musician forced to earn additionally in unimportant bars. But success which came to lovers begins to undermine their relations.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Comedy       Drama       Music       Musical       Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 09:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Green Book</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/899-green-book-v8.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/899-green-book-v8.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[At one point, a sophisticated socialite, a wealthy and very talented musician realizes the need for a personal driver and a real bodyguard. The plot of "Green Book" he employs a person who is not suited for the job. In fact, Tony "Loudmouth" is a bouncer, whose language without bones. His finger in your mouth, give only chat on any topic. But with all this, it keeps the beat and wonderful waving fists. It is with such a man embarks on a tour of the musician that will forever change the lives of both heroes.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Comedy        Biography        Drama        Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 15:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>A Star Is Born</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/896-a-star-is-born-v4.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/896-a-star-is-born-v4.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Jackson Maine is a famous country musician who feels a certain creative crisis. Once the protagonist meets a future rising star, an aspiring singer named Emily. Between a man and a woman are generated real feelings that escalate into a turbulent love affair. Jackson helps Emily to win their place in the Music Scene. He is doing his best to make her career ascended the mountain by leaps and bounds. But, for all that he is well aware that its own glory and success slowly fade and fade into the background.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Drama         Music         Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 15:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bohemian Rhapsody</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/402-bohemian-rhapsody-v6.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/402-bohemian-rhapsody-v6.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Biographical drama "Bohemian Rhapsody" tells about the life and work of an outstanding lead vocalist Freddie Mercury and the legendary band Queen is one of the most successful rock bands in music history, which broke stereotypes that went beyond the strict framework of prudish Britain blasted world of music and has gained millions of fans. But the path to fame Freddie and his friends musicians was not easy, but a truly dizzying.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Biography          Drama          Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 14:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>How the Beatles Changed the World</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/813-how-the-beatles-changed-the-world.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/813-how-the-beatles-changed-the-world.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The history of The Beatles and their influence on everything from music, art, and culture to fashion and politics.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           History           Music]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 16:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>