<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Musical - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Musical - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Smallfoot</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/236-smallfoot-v23.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["Smallfoot" overturns the myth of bigfutah upside down. In it a young resourceful Yeti is faced with the fact that his deep conviction that there is no man. News on "smolfute" brought him fame and a chance to win the girl of his dreams. And yet-cause a stir among ordinary Yeti who now wonder what else lives in the big world outside their small snowbound villages.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Animation  Comedy  Family  Fantasy  Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 11:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>I Can Only Imagine</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1767-i-can-only-imagine.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1767-i-can-only-imagine.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[History of the birth of the song of the same name of the MercyMe group. The team leader devoted this song about belief, love and forgiveness to the father, without suspecting that it will fly about the whole world soon, will become a platinum hit, and, above all — will present hope to millions of people.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Biography   Drama   Family   Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 19:44:31 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Pup Star: World Tour</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1723-pup-star-world-tour.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1723-pup-star-world-tour.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[And what if dogs can react to the voice team in a different way? It is not simple to begin a bark, and to create the musical show with judges and stars having a tail? But even in it, it would seem the ideal creative world, there can be a competition and mean plots.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Comedy    Family    Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 18:13:24 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Frozen</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1700-frozen.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1700-frozen.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[On a birthday of Anna, Elza and Christoff are full of determination to present it the best holiday made ever, but ice forces of Elza can do more harm, than the organization of a holiday.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Animation     Comedy     Family     Fantasy     Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 19:31:51 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Fits</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1685-the-fits.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1685-the-fits.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The teenage girl began to visit new sports section. First everything is pleasant to it, it approaches other girls of the team, but then she notices that most of them often faint and test strange nervous attacks.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Drama      Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 18:46:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Theory of Obscurity: A Film About the Residents</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1616-theory-of-obscurity-a-film-about-the-residents.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1616-theory-of-obscurity-a-film-about-the-residents.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The Residents are known first of all for the reserve. The famous art group which affected ten giants in the field of music and art: KLF, Tuxedomoon, Animal Collective — was a pioneer in work with multimedia, and its management the company under the name The Cryptic Corporation is engaged to this day, building more and more indistinct mythology about participants of mystical structure. Authors of the movie swept with The Residents in an anniversary USA and Europe tour in honor of the 40 anniversary of existence of group, and then interviewed musicians including from Talking Heads and Devo, fans, musical critics, those on whom The Residents had the impact to understand how the phenomenon which was consciously avoiding popularity and keeping anonymity within 40 years managed to change shape of today's mass culture.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 19:03:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Road Chip</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1572-alvin-and-the-chipmunks-the-road-chip.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1572-alvin-and-the-chipmunks-the-road-chip.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Chipmunks will be ready to do anything to keep the family, even on a grandiose burunduklyucheniye across all America!<br><br>When Chipmunks see that Dave takes with himself a box with a ring in a trip to Miami, they desperately try to prevent it to make the proposal to his girl — for fear that the stepmother and the stepbrother will bring changes in their family idyll. But after they are placed in the black list for hooligan behavior on the plane, Alvin, Simon, Theodor and their future brother Miles go to the most important travel to their lives through the whole country to manage to prevent an engagement.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Adventure        Animation        Comedy        Family        Fantasy        Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:22:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Ricki and the Flash</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1571-ricki-and-the-flash.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1571-ricki-and-the-flash.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[History of the extravagant creative person which unexpectedly returns to the house to the ex-husband many years of life later far from it and children.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Comedy         Drama         Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:20:47 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Daft Punk Unchained</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1564-daft-punk-unchained.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1564-daft-punk-unchained.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie tells about history formation of the legendary French electronic Daft Punk duet, about turning points and contains an interview of people as which has the luck to work with group for the last 20 years in his career.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:56:45 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>All Things Must Pass: The Rise and Fall of Tower Records</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1548-all-things-must-pass-the-rise-and-fall-of-tower-records.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1548-all-things-must-pass-the-rise-and-fall-of-tower-records.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The network of musical shops Tower Records is an example of successful business, the real American dream. The company opened in 1960 in the capital of California – the city of Sacramento, and gradually gained steam. The organization developed and opened branches in 35 countries on all continents of Earth. In these shops came to enjoy the atmosphere, to chat about favourite music and to buy new plates, cartridges and disks. Network shops Tower Records had a considerable impact not only on listeners, but also on musicians. In 1996 turnover of the company made more than one billion dollars. It seemed that it only the beginning of a new era for shop. But unexpectedly for all in 2006 the network went bankrupt. What became the reason? It would be possible to save the company?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           History           Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 20:32:49 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>