<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Crime - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Crime - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>One on One</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Oh-Hyun is a young guy who is a hired killer, working for an influential criminal group. He always brings the case to the end and never being torments of conscience, because for him it's just a job. The next order of his boss, who always pays good money, he becomes a murder of a young schoolgirl, and o-Hyung as always impeccably performs its work. However, he then falls into the hands of unknown to him, dressed in military uniforms, who begin to torture him, trying to learn the name of those who ordered the girl. In addition to on-Hena under suspicion to fall a few more people, and violent the Avengers will not rest until each and every one of them will be punished.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Crime  Drama  Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>We Are Young. We Are Strong.</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1889-we-are-young-we-are-strong.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Rostock in August 1992 year. The situation in the port city, which after the fall of the Berlin wall is not the best of times and suffers from massive unemployment, is heating up with every second. All dissatisfaction with radical residents refer to "home with sunflowers" — giant building, which houses a youth hostel and a camp for Vietnamese seeking asylum in Germany as refugees. The film traces the story of three Heroes: a young Vietnamese Lin, dreaming of a better future, young Stephen, which falls into the company of neo-Nazis, and his father, Martin-local politics-Democrat trying to maneuver between the need to carry responsibility for what is happening and the desire to preserve reputation.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Crime   Drama   History]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:00:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Ek Villain</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Guru-ruthless and cruel, the machine working on the political system. In his life, he committed the unimaginable things that now do not give him peace. It is in crisis, from which no exit-anyway, he does not see. Insomnia is a common State for the hero. Meditations on morality increasingly annoys him.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Action    Crime    Drama    Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:57:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Drive Hard</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1877-drive-hard.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1877-drive-hard.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the not-too-distant past, the character of John Cusack professional motor racing, but as time passed, the former glory and now the man is forced to go to rest. Peter got a driving instructor, allowing you to indulge in a favorite activity, while not risking their lives at enormous speeds. True, if the fate of plans to bring in a person's life the next test of fortitude, you no names of upcoming events.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Action     Comedy     Crime]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:22:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>John Wick: Chapter 3 - Parabellum</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1866-john-wick-chapter-3-parabellum-v2.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1866-john-wick-chapter-3-parabellum-v2.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[John Wick as a professional Hitman, decides to change his life and get back on the right path. All was well until his house is committed the attack, an unknown offender hijacked a car and shot the beloved dog, only the memory of the deceased spouse. Man falls into a rage from the incident, he did not intend to tolerate, it develops a thirst for revenge. Craziest began chasing the hero for posmevshim to invade his life nedobrozhelatelem. He pursues a potential enemy to the New Yorker, there he acquainted with the ringleaders of criminal business, which offered him a deal. After John broke the secret code of the Guild, it expelled from the gang and he becomes an outcast in society. Moreover, for the capture of the hero of the comic not assigned price, fourteen million dollars, whether dead or alive, but it must be delivered to the leader of the group. Many dream cut easy money, thanks to Wick, the most courageous and professional assassin, who in the past were colleagues of John hunt for his head. Whether the man alone to confront bloody crack or so and will hide all along deserted places.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Action      Crime      Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:20:18 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Mule</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1863-the-mule.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1863-the-mule.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Earl Stone is a World War II veteran who dreamed that seniors will live a quiet life surrounded by children and grandchildren, pursuing their own business. Man a lot invested in the development of the case, but the ninth top ten remained with nothing. Relationship with his wife deteriorated definitively, relatives have forgotten about the bamboo, and the business soon closed.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Crime       Drama       Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 08:06:17 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>No Country for Old Men</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1856-no-country-for-old-men.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1856-no-country-for-old-men.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Movie plot evolves in Texas in June 1980 year. Crime in the region is growing at breakneck speed, and criminals are becoming increasingly cruel and inhumane. The protagonist Llvelin Moss, a veteran of the Vietnam war, embarks on a hunt near the Rio Grande. There, he stumbles upon a mountain of corpses shot machines, drugs and a bunch of money. Apparently this was a shoot-out between gangs of drug traffickers. At prihvativshego with an apparently the main character of the problems start from which he can not escape.<br><br>]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Crime        Drama        Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 11:22:51 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Paterno</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Petter is a typical teenager, it is betrayed loving the father and mother. His father was the owner of the detective agency until recently. Soon the agency went bankrupt and it had to be closed. St. Petersburg family suffered serious financial losses. The son sharply endured defeat of the father. The man hard was given the decision to close the agency, but an exit was not. It is sensitive having sat and having thought, Peter finds the solution how to help the father. He wants to restore the detective agency. Understanding that alone he will hardly manage to cope, the boy takes in assistants to a faithful doggie and parrot who as it became clear later, are able to talk. After a while friends get to epicenter of serious opposition with the most dangerous person in the city.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Crime         Biography         Drama         Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:15:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Daphne &amp; Velma</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1838-daphne-amp-velma.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1838-daphne-amp-velma.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[<span>Two girlfriends, future employees of the mysterious organization "Misteri Ink.", try to understand the devilry which is created at their school.</span>]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Action          Comedy          Crime          Horror          Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:25:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Hurricane Heist</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1835-the-hurricane-heist.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1835-the-hurricane-heist.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The hurricane promptly approaches the coast of America. Meanwhile the gang of thieves plans ideal robbery: to steal 600 million dollars from the U.S. Treasury, having used natural disaster as cover. But robbers have not considered one factor — the honest and prepared worker of treasury. The woman unites with the researcher of hurricanes on the specialized armored car in time, and now they — only who can prevent thieves to carry out the plan of robbery. Almost only, for hurricane out of categories there is no division on personal and others'.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Action           Crime           Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:10:25 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>