<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Horror - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Horror - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>As the Gods Will</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The action of the action-movie "As the Gods Will" takes place in our days in Japan. A teenager named sun Takahata is studying in high school, and unlike his peers, he is not quite happy with his life, because it seems to him boring and monotonous. The guy dreams that something extraordinary and memorable happened. And once the desire Suna implemented, but not as he had imagined. The school begins to appear strange live toys that offer students to play a variety of games. At first glance, everything looks harmless, but in reality it is not so simple. Toys, which is headed by the ancient God the Dolls are actually do not leave children, since those who refused to play, the result will meet the same fate as the loser certain death. Those who still manage to win, will be given life. Here is only will whether such?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Horror  Sci-Fi  Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>What We Do in the Shadows</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1882-what-we-do-in-the-shadows.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The film tells the story of the life of three neighbors in the apartment: silent and strict Vladislav, mannered Viagra and extremely active Deacon. They are immortal vampires and try to adapt to the modern conditions of life in the small town of Wellington. Earlier the main problem all the vampires were killing the light of the sun and not uragement in any mirrors. So survival was more or less real. And even outlive many of the annoying hunters. But now other times have come, and everything has changed dramatically. The unfortunate trio is not so easy to adapt, because they are haunted by exorbitant rent, ubiquitous sunlight and who knows who invented face control in bars and clubs. In addition, there are a lot of other various troubles: from annoying hospitable residents in the neighborhood to daily washing dishes...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Comedy   Horror]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:59 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bermuda Tentacles</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[American Fantasy horror film (Bermuda Tentacles) can find a response in the soul of even the most sophisticated cinephile. The action unfolds on kinoistorii sea Bermuda triangle. Peaceful ship quietly goes to the coveted military objective-to shore. But it is precisely at the moment of calm and serenity in the way the vessel is raised sea monster is bulky, the stench of foul, heartbreaking. And then ship the AIR FORCE will have to maintain an unequal battle with the sea giant. All possible forces and guns. Bermuda tentacles leave no choice: fight or die.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Action    Comedy    Horror    Sci-Fi    Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:08 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Stranger</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[As a rule, vampires are bloodthirsty and unscrupulous monsters, without special moral principles and restrictions. But Martin – the protagonist of this film, it is not so. And even you can not guess about his vampire life, because it behaves like a normal person.  Vampirism your character perceives painful as deadly, incurable disease... But may still have some remedy? It is for this Martin embarks on a journey to my once native city. He needs to find a woman named Anna, but she died a long time ago…]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Drama     Horror     Mystery     Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:59:28 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Wolves</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[One day, waking up at night, the protagonist finds his murdered parents. Having decided that it was his handiwork, the guy turns into a wild Wolf and leaves home. The true reason for leaving the hero from home-an unfair accusation Caleb murder their own parents. He did not commit, however, forced to hide in a safe place in town called Wolf Ridge. As it turns out, this place is filled with mysticism and is inextricably linked to the secret family guy by Caleb will have to unravel. The life of a young man no longer will be the same, because the entire responsibility he learns his true purpose in life.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Action      Fantasy      Horror      Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:57:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Hellboy</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1865-hellboy.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1865-hellboy.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Powerful and insane Nimue, enlightening centuries later, intends to arrange the Apocalypse and plunge mankind into chaos. The hero of the movie to fight the hordes of evil, which called itself the Queen for help. Sometimes it seems that the guy can't do this an impossible mission. The girl turns out to be the wife of the great Wizard Merlin. Of course, fight alone with this enemy cannot and battle with evil our Sapphire will assist a team of people, each of whom is a professional.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Action       Fantasy       Horror       Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 09:19:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Us</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1860-us.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1860-us.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Married couple embarks on a long-awaited vacations with the children. They have long planned to spend the holiday together and even agreed with friends, where exactly will rest. The road to the beach was pretty long, but finally they have reached the right place and moved into a rented house. Now nothing can stop them enjoy, forget about all your everyday problems and concerns. They had a great day, but at night it becomes clear to them that quiet time is left behind. The thing is that before their house appeared uninvited guests who are not going to go away until they take away their lives. The strangest thing that they look exactly like they know in advance all their actions. Will the family be saved from themselves?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Horror        Mystery        Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:56:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Edge of Isolation</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1845-edge-of-isolation.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1845-edge-of-isolation.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Walks on forests not always bring benefit to their participants. The young couple has gone to the nature, however on the road they were found by unpleasant surprise. Practically under wheels of the car the half-naked man has run out that has led to accident. Lovers in the unfamiliar room where surprising people live have regained consciousness. They gain income due to robberies and murders. How has existence of the similar organization in the developed society become possible? What prospects of the neighbourhood with unpredictable savages? Whether inhabitants will get out to freedom? Why have not dealt shortly with them at once? What will be way home?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Drama         Horror         Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:05:06 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Revenge of Robert the Doll</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1843-the-revenge-of-robert-the-doll.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1843-the-revenge-of-robert-the-doll.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Paulo and Jane were necessary to calculate the aging housekeeper Agata who became more and more forgetful and spiteful. The dissatisfied old woman before departure presented to the son of the former owners a doll which call Robert. After Agata's departure in the house inexplicable things begin to occur. Someone spoils furniture, breaks ware, destroys a picture on which Jane worked. Moreover and at night spiteful laughter which source cannot be found sounds. Only their son Gene claims that the doll is guilty of all this, but nobody trusts him. The doll absolutely flies from coils — it begins to kill …]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Horror]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 16:56:47 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Dead List</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1840-dead-list.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1840-dead-list.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Having got acquainted with the book the friend found out that the book contains an interesting ritual which will help to sentence people to death. It is necessary to make only the list of those whom you want to eliminate after the journey — further everything will occur by itself! This opportunity inspires the unlucky actor. He quickly makes the list of the competitors after whose death will remain the only applicant for a role of the dream. Now he should reap the fruits of the artful act...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Comedy           Horror]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 16:43:47 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>