<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Sport - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Sport - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Paterno</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Petter is a typical teenager, it is betrayed loving the father and mother. His father was the owner of the detective agency until recently. Soon the agency went bankrupt and it had to be closed. St. Petersburg family suffered serious financial losses. The son sharply endured defeat of the father. The man hard was given the decision to close the agency, but an exit was not. It is sensitive having sat and having thought, Peter finds the solution how to help the father. He wants to restore the detective agency. Understanding that alone he will hardly manage to cope, the boy takes in assistants to a faithful doggie and parrot who as it became clear later, are able to talk. After a while friends get to epicenter of serious opposition with the most dangerous person in the city.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Crime  Biography  Drama  Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:15:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Alex &amp; Me</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1712-alex-amp-me.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1712-alex-amp-me.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["Alex and I" is an inspiring story about passion and the tselustremlennost, necessary to succeed, and force of family which can help to embody any dream.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Family   Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 17:13:37 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Amateur</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1709-amateur.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1709-amateur.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The basketball player Theron gets chance to prove to be. The place in prestigious team where there is everything for development is provided to it: excellent trainer, halls for trainings, equipment. But to what Terron should go to become the professional player?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Drama    Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 17:04:55 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Being AP</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1457-being-ap.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1457-being-ap.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[This. is the incredible inside story of a sporting legend. As A.P. McCoy nears the end of his career, the characteristics that have driven him to dominate the most dangerous of sports remain as strong as ever. Fearless and willing to sacrifice everything to achieve his goals, this film reveals the exhaustive training routine, injuries, doubt, triumphs, failures, and A.P.'s soul-searching to find a way to leave the stage. With unprecedented access to A.P. and those closest to him, this documentary. celebrates an incredible man who became the greatest jump jockey the world has ever seen.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 17:07:38 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Bronze</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1452-the-bronze.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1452-the-bronze.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Hope Ann Gregory nearly from the cradle did gymnastics. She persistently trained, in everything limited herself and the top of its achievements — bronze at the Olympic Games 2004 dreamed to become the champion, but. And a trauma in addition which gave up as a bad job sports career.<br><br>Ten years later Hope lives all in the same small town where her each dog knows, wears the same sports suit, eats too much fast food, talks smut and constantly swears at the father. Absolutely idealistic, without occupations, hobbies and the purposes, she after all considers herself the local hero. Suddenly her former trainer commits a suicide, and Hope has chance to train a rising star of gymnastics from its town. And whether the competition to already taken place hero is necessary? Most likely - No.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Comedy      Drama      Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 16:59:43 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Program</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1415-the-program.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1415-the-program.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The Irish sports journalist is convinced that Lance Armstrong during the victorious performances on Tour de France used the forbidden substances. With these beliefs he begins to look for proofs which will expose Armstrong.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Biography       Drama       Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 18:45:43 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>I Believe in Miracles</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1384-i-believe-in-miracles.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1384-i-believe-in-miracles.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[History of legendary English football club "Nottingham Forest".]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        History        Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 18:02:09 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Mr Calzaghe</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1359-mr-calzaghe.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1359-mr-calzaghe.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie is devoted to the former world champion in the second average weight, to the Welshman Joe Calzaghe, and his trainer, the father Enzo. Joe most longer in the history owned a champion title in superaverage weight — more than ten years, at 21 successful protection. In February, 2009 Calzaghe hung up gloves on a nail undefeated in 46 fights, at 32 early victories.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Biography         Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 17:31:24 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Eddie the Eagle</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1348-eddie-the-eagle.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1348-eddie-the-eagle.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The movie narrates about Eddie's tramplinist, known as Oryol. It became famous thanks to the failures because at all competitions he took the last places.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Comedy          Biography          Drama          Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 19:21:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Meru</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1331-meru.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1331-meru.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In October, 2008 climbers Conrad Anker, Jimmy Chin and Renan Oztyurk arrived in India for ascension on peak to Mer, on the well-known northeast slope of Meru Central (6630 m) along a route of "Shark" s Fin". The planned seven-day trip turned into heavy three-week fight for top. In 100 meters the group was forced to recede from top — as well as all who tried to pass a route to them. But in September, 2011 Conrad Anker convinced the team to try once again …]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Action           Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 18:31:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>