<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Action - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Action - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1701-avengers-endgame.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1701-avengers-endgame.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The plot of the movie "Avengers: Endgame" tells about the events after Thanos was able to carry out his plan. Half Vmelennoj evaporate and now nobody knows what will happen next. Naturally the situation is not the best way, and many have lost their loved ones. Stark is committed in another world and no one knows if he is alive. The same is happening on the ground is a real mess. Many people do not believe that someday will be able to fix something, but do it. The Avengers lost their war and it seems that there is no way out of the situation. But give up they are just not going. Will have to challenge the mad Titan and try to win this time. To do so would be extremely difficult and complicated, but it is to rely on the positive result. Only by bringing all his forces together, they will be able to strike, which would probably fix this whole situation. Ahead of their final battle, in which each character would try to participate. What this all will end and whether they will oppose such a strong enemy? Once failed, so it is not known why this all will lead! War is only just beginning and is nearing the most finals, which will put an end to this confrontation.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Fantasy  Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 17:12:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1898-captain-america-the-winter-soldier.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1898-captain-america-the-winter-soldier.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[After the event, bringing together a team of Avengers, Captain America decides to stay in Washington. He has tried its best to adapt to the modern world, which has changed a lot over that time, while Steve was frozen. But the quiet life he had dreamed about, and soon he finds himself in the center of events that could lead to global catastrophe. Realizing that stop villains alone would be very uneasy, Captain America joins forces with the black widow, and later joins them and another hero, known to all as the Falcon. However, none of their teams cannot even imagine, what a terrible force has their new enemy.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Adventure   Action   Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:39:23 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1897-guardians-of-the-galaxy.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1897-guardians-of-the-galaxy.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[While still a child, the protagonist Peter Quill becomes a victim of kidnapping by extraterrestrials. As an adult, he takes the nickname Star Lord and turns into one of the most legendary bandits throughout the Galaxy, but, at least, he thinks so. Once Peter in SED mysterious and very powerful artifact, owned by the powerful and knowledgeable not pity villain Ronan, who yearns to capture the universe. However, there are still others who wants the artifact, resulting in Peter turns out to be a victim of intergalactic hunting. Ahead of his many breathtaking adventure, meeting new friends, with whom they have to work together to save the Galaxy.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Action    Comedy    Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 16:10:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Transformers: Age of Extinction</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1896-transformers-age-of-extinction.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1896-transformers-age-of-extinction.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Four years have passed since the last events. Then during clashes between Autobots and Decepticons enormous Chicago was virtually fully destroyed, and millions of people died. After this incident, humanity has radically changed its attitude to all transformers without exception. People have learned a good lesson from all that has happened, and to prevent this from happening again, a group of scientists and businessmen manage to reach a completely new technological level.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Action     Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:10:31 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Monkey King</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1892-the-monkey-king.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1892-the-monkey-king.html</link>
<description><![CDATA["The Monkey King" is based on ancient Chinese mythology, according to which Buddhism appeared according to this legend. The story in the film will be about the popular character of Chinese youth and in children's literature the monkey King. His personality is complex and contradictory: playful and sad, heroic and comic. The film tells the story of three worlds (demons, people and heaven). In immemorial times, demons, who decided to seize the sky, lost in combat and were is banished. The heavens suffered with a view to their recovery one of the gods sacrificed himself. To archaeologist nick Orton, during an expedition to China, was the goddess Kwan Yin with a request. The fate of the whole world is at stake. You want to find an ancient monuscript, which was stolen by demons and rescue from captivity monkey King, who is in prison for five hundred years. San Wukong (the monkey king) was born from drops of tears of the goddess who saved the Sky. Temptations began to Eclipse his soul, he learns his strength and destroys the castle in which he was born. For this he was punished by the Gods and sent to prison.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Adventure      Action      Family]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:05:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Captain America: The First Avenger</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1891-captain-america-the-first-avenger.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1891-captain-america-the-first-avenger.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Fantastic action movie directed by Joe Johnston, which formed the plot of the same name comics publisher "Marvel Comics". The action takes place in the midst of the Second World war. The hero of the film Steve Rogers very much wants to get into the army, but due to the fact that the guy is very thin and looks sick, it does not take. But one day his wish in some measure come to pass, and he becomes a party to the selection, for a place in a secret military experiment, in which with the help of a special serum and radiation Guinea pig needs to turn into a super soldier. Thanks to their dedication and courage Steve is the selection and turn it into a real fighting machine. The guy begins to perform various dangerous tasks for his country under the pseudonym "Captain America". However, ahead of him waiting for the confrontation with a very strong and dangerous enemy, eager to take over the world.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Action       Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:03:38 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Ek Villain</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Guru-ruthless and cruel, the machine working on the political system. In his life, he committed the unimaginable things that now do not give him peace. It is in crisis, from which no exit-anyway, he does not see. Insomnia is a common State for the hero. Meditations on morality increasingly annoys him.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Action        Crime        Drama        Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:57:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Fatal Encounter</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1885-the-fatal-encounter.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1885-the-fatal-encounter.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The story of conspiracy and murder, about the fate of those who are destined to live or die, be saved or be faithful. The plot expands around the life of King Jeongjo of Joseon in the Joseon era.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Action         Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 20:28:47 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Avengers</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1884-the-avengers.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1884-the-avengers.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[On the ground gets an extraterrestrial source of inexhaustible energy Tesserkat. A team of scientists exploring the unknown material takes S.h.i.e.l.d. into their own hands. After the study, astrophysicist Eric Selvig informs the Director of Fury that the tesseract is not stable, and could happen at any time such a powerful burst of energy that all living creatures will disappear from the face of the Earth. When the cube is activated, it opens the gates between the worlds, through which the Earth gets adopted son Loki god Odin. He picks up Tesserkat, and Eric Selviga and Clint Barton, nicknamed "Hawkeye". Agents are sent followed by Loki, because their mind is subject to his will through the magical skipetru. Referring to the looming threat of Fury decides to revive the Avengers initiative project, previously canceled for unexplained reasons.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Adventure          Action          Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 11:11:36 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bermuda Tentacles</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[American Fantasy horror film (Bermuda Tentacles) can find a response in the soul of even the most sophisticated cinephile. The action unfolds on kinoistorii sea Bermuda triangle. Peaceful ship quietly goes to the coveted military objective-to shore. But it is precisely at the moment of calm and serenity in the way the vessel is raised sea monster is bulky, the stench of foul, heartbreaking. And then ship the AIR FORCE will have to maintain an unequal battle with the sea giant. All possible forces and guns. Bermuda tentacles leave no choice: fight or die.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Adventure           Action           Comedy           Horror           Sci-Fi           Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:08 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>