<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Thriller - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Thriller - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>As the Gods Will</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1894-as-the-gods-will.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The action of the action-movie "As the Gods Will" takes place in our days in Japan. A teenager named sun Takahata is studying in high school, and unlike his peers, he is not quite happy with his life, because it seems to him boring and monotonous. The guy dreams that something extraordinary and memorable happened. And once the desire Suna implemented, but not as he had imagined. The school begins to appear strange live toys that offer students to play a variety of games. At first glance, everything looks harmless, but in reality it is not so simple. Toys, which is headed by the ancient God the Dolls are actually do not leave children, since those who refused to play, the result will meet the same fate as the loser certain death. Those who still manage to win, will be given life. Here is only will whether such?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Horror  Sci-Fi  Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:08:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>One on One</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1890-one-on-one.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Oh-Hyun is a young guy who is a hired killer, working for an influential criminal group. He always brings the case to the end and never being torments of conscience, because for him it's just a job. The next order of his boss, who always pays good money, he becomes a murder of a young schoolgirl, and o-Hyung as always impeccably performs its work. However, he then falls into the hands of unknown to him, dressed in military uniforms, who begin to torture him, trying to learn the name of those who ordered the girl. In addition to on-Hena under suspicion to fall a few more people, and violent the Avengers will not rest until each and every one of them will be punished.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Crime   Drama   Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 11:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Ek Villain</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1887-ek-villain.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Guru-ruthless and cruel, the machine working on the political system. In his life, he committed the unimaginable things that now do not give him peace. It is in crisis, from which no exit-anyway, he does not see. Insomnia is a common State for the hero. Meditations on morality increasingly annoys him.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Action    Crime    Drama    Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 10:57:30 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bermuda Tentacles</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1881-bermuda-tentacles.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[American Fantasy horror film (Bermuda Tentacles) can find a response in the soul of even the most sophisticated cinephile. The action unfolds on kinoistorii sea Bermuda triangle. Peaceful ship quietly goes to the coveted military objective-to shore. But it is precisely at the moment of calm and serenity in the way the vessel is raised sea monster is bulky, the stench of foul, heartbreaking. And then ship the AIR FORCE will have to maintain an unequal battle with the sea giant. All possible forces and guns. Bermuda tentacles leave no choice: fight or die.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Action     Comedy     Horror     Sci-Fi     Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:27:08 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Prince</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1880-the-prince.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1880-the-prince.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[American thriller "The Prince" brought together in its composition of remarkable actors of contemporary Cinematography: Bruce Willis, Jason Patrick, John Cusack. But the main advantage of the film are, without doubt, an interesting storyline, entertainment and dynamic pictures. The protagonist is at first glance an ordinary mechanic. He repairs the machine, than earn their living themselves and beloved daughter. Daughter left to study in another city, but every day calls up with his father and it seems that their little family all safely. But one day his father receive a letter from the College that his daughter is expelled, and the girl stops to go. What remains to do man? Of course, go in search of the same (by the way, his native) city! Where he is sent, taking with a couple of pistols and girlfriend of missing daughter. Suddenly it turns out that the girl had consumed drugs her and kidnapped. But the Pope is not so simple-chasing the kidnappers follows his criminal past. The plot keeps in suspense throughout the film, perfectly matched soundtracks, acting at the highest level-all components of upscale militants there.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Action      Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:26:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bang Bang</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1879-bang-bang.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1879-bang-bang.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the blockbuster "Bang Bang", you'll see an exciting narrative about a girl Harlin Sahni. She is an employee of the Bank, the dreamer who can love and be sexy. This girl is pure and innocent and at the same time. She accidentally meets an attractive and full of mystery Radzhivira Rand. It is open, risky and attractive. And he immediately falls into the soul of the girl. This meeting leads to an exciting adventure. Harlin learns that Radzhivir former spy trying to clear his name, but it turns out he is not very good. Explosions, shootouts, chases and complete chaos. That's what happens to make Radzhiviru. But, despite all this Bedlam and chaos, he leaves to convince Harlin in that he is not a bad guy. But whether Harlin trust him? And is it worth it? And how can he reclaim his name? Though the film is a thriller, but at the same time, full of love, romance and passion. Also in the movie there are a lot of comedy and humor. Captivating storyline intrigue until the end, holding the film. All of the above and good actors is, just what you're looking for a good movie]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Action       Comedy       Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 13:25:03 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Stranger</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[As a rule, vampires are bloodthirsty and unscrupulous monsters, without special moral principles and restrictions. But Martin – the protagonist of this film, it is not so. And even you can not guess about his vampire life, because it behaves like a normal person.  Vampirism your character perceives painful as deadly, incurable disease... But may still have some remedy? It is for this Martin embarks on a journey to my once native city. He needs to find a woman named Anna, but she died a long time ago…]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Drama        Horror        Mystery        Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:59:28 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Wolves</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1871-wolves.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[One day, waking up at night, the protagonist finds his murdered parents. Having decided that it was his handiwork, the guy turns into a wild Wolf and leaves home. The true reason for leaving the hero from home-an unfair accusation Caleb murder their own parents. He did not commit, however, forced to hide in a safe place in town called Wolf Ridge. As it turns out, this place is filled with mysticism and is inextricably linked to the secret family guy by Caleb will have to unravel. The life of a young man no longer will be the same, because the entire responsibility he learns his true purpose in life.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Action         Fantasy         Horror         Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:57:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Guvnors</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1870-the-guvnors.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1870-the-guvnors.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The film Daddy (The Guvnors) unfolds on the streets of Southwest London. Young lives, divided into clans, led them scumbags, cruel and cynical, seeking to impose its strict laws of life. With provinivshimisja they mercilessly massacred, whether this guy or girl. Parents do not report to the police, not believing that there will be a Government Act. Law enforcement officials remember and appreciate leaders that have become legends. With them you can solve many serious problems. Present the same dregs were not peers.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:55:54 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>John Wick: Chapter 3 - Parabellum</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1866-john-wick-chapter-3-parabellum-v2.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1866-john-wick-chapter-3-parabellum-v2.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[John Wick as a professional Hitman, decides to change his life and get back on the right path. All was well until his house is committed the attack, an unknown offender hijacked a car and shot the beloved dog, only the memory of the deceased spouse. Man falls into a rage from the incident, he did not intend to tolerate, it develops a thirst for revenge. Craziest began chasing the hero for posmevshim to invade his life nedobrozhelatelem. He pursues a potential enemy to the New Yorker, there he acquainted with the ringleaders of criminal business, which offered him a deal. After John broke the secret code of the Guild, it expelled from the gang and he becomes an outcast in society. Moreover, for the capture of the hero of the comic not assigned price, fourteen million dollars, whether dead or alive, but it must be delivered to the leader of the group. Many dream cut easy money, thanks to Wick, the most courageous and professional assassin, who in the past were colleagues of John hunt for his head. Whether the man alone to confront bloody crack or so and will hide all along deserted places.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Action           Crime           Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:20:18 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>