<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Biography - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Biography - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Paterno</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1849-paterno.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Petter is a typical teenager, it is betrayed loving the father and mother. His father was the owner of the detective agency until recently. Soon the agency went bankrupt and it had to be closed. St. Petersburg family suffered serious financial losses. The son sharply endured defeat of the father. The man hard was given the decision to close the agency, but an exit was not. It is sensitive having sat and having thought, Peter finds the solution how to help the father. He wants to restore the detective agency. Understanding that alone he will hardly manage to cope, the boy takes in assistants to a faithful doggie and parrot who as it became clear later, are able to talk. After a while friends get to epicenter of serious opposition with the most dangerous person in the city.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Crime  Biography  Drama  Sport]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 17:15:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Winchester</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1774-winchester.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1774-winchester.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Sara Vinchester, the successor of the well-known weapon company, lives in the grandiose building which architecture does not give in to logic, and corridors are similar to labyrinths. According to the order of the inconsolable widow the mansion is constantly reconstructed and new walls are infinitely erected. But she builds not for herself, not for the niece or talented doctor Eric Price who arrived to the mansion by her invitation. Sara builds a trap for hundreds of vindictive ghosts, and the most terrible of them want to deal shortly with clan of Winchesters.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Biography   Drama   Fantasy   Horror   Mystery   Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 19:59:32 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>I Can Only Imagine</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1767-i-can-only-imagine.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1767-i-can-only-imagine.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[History of the birth of the song of the same name of the MercyMe group. The team leader devoted this song about belief, love and forgiveness to the father, without suspecting that it will fly about the whole world soon, will become a platinum hit, and, above all — will present hope to millions of people.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Biography    Drama    Family    Musical]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 19:44:31 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Simone Biles Story: Courage to Soar</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1755-the-simone-biles-story-courage-to-soar.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1755-the-simone-biles-story-courage-to-soar.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[This documentary will please fans of sport in general and to admirers of artistic gymnastics in particular. He will tell fascinating story of formation of a young star of big-time sports which in 20 years became the four-time Olympic champion and the ten-time world champion.<br>Since the childhood of Simon raved gymnastics. It systematically went to achievement of a goal. For the sake of it she threw school as she could not combine together heavy physical activities and study. On the thorny road this courageous girl experienced many difficulties which she overcame.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Biography]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 19:29:36 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Harry &amp; Meghan: A Royal Romance</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1737-harry-amp-meghan-a-royal-romance.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1737-harry-amp-meghan-a-royal-romance.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The love story of the English prince Harry and American actress the Megane Markl telling about couple relations from the date of their acquaintance.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Biography      Drama      Romance]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 18:21:44 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Paul, Apostle of Christ</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1721-paul-apostle-of-christ.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1721-paul-apostle-of-christ.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Life story and the death of the apostle Pavel who passed a way from the ruthless persecutor of Christians to one of founders of Christian church. Its last missionary travel comes to an end in prison where it was заточён by order of the Roman emperor Neron. While the captivated Pavel waits for an execution and reflects on the posthumous fate, his follower Luka writes the new Gospel.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Adventure       Biography       Drama       History]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 18:05:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Mercy</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1708-the-mercy.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1708-the-mercy.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In 1968 the British amateur yachtsman Donald Kroukhyorst, having put all the state, decided to fulfill a dream of all life, having made alone a risky round-the-world trip within a regatta for a prize of the Sunday Times newspaper. Soon after departure he understood that to it not to win this competition, and conceived absolutely mad adventure.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Adventure        Biography        Drama        Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 17:03:13 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Stanford Prison Experiment</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1696-the-stanford-prison-experiment.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1696-the-stanford-prison-experiment.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The experiment of the American psychologist is the basis for the movie. He chose volunteers who played a role of supervisors and prisoners, and arranged them in one case the real prison. People quickly accustomed and, to huge surprise of the psychologist, began to behave is unpredictable. What will lead the experiment which got out of hand to?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Biography         Drama         History         Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 19:13:15 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Memoria</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1689-memoria.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1689-memoria.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The guy from California by the name of Iwan Coen in every way tries to find the place in life. He loves the girl who to know knows nothing about it. And his friends are full idlers. And the family does not indulge him. Here the guy also tries to understand all events alone!]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Biography          Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 18:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The End of the Tour</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1614-the-end-of-the-tour.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1614-the-end-of-the-tour.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Soon after the publication of the novel "Infinite Joke" (is later than the 20th century which entered the list of hundred best novels according to Time) the writer David Foster Wallace goes to a trip with the journalist of Rolling Stone David Lipski, preparing about it article. In five days between them there was a certain confidential communication which allowed each of them to share the intimate thoughts and desires. Anyway, the interview was never published — audio cassettes went to Lipski's case, and heroes so it is more and did not meet.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Biography           Drama]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 18:59:45 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>