<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Mystery - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Mystery - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>The Stranger</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1873-the-stranger.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[As a rule, vampires are bloodthirsty and unscrupulous monsters, without special moral principles and restrictions. But Martin – the protagonist of this film, it is not so. And even you can not guess about his vampire life, because it behaves like a normal person.  Vampirism your character perceives painful as deadly, incurable disease... But may still have some remedy? It is for this Martin embarks on a journey to my once native city. He needs to find a woman named Anna, but she died a long time ago…]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Drama  Horror  Mystery  Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 09:59:28 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Us</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1860-us.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1860-us.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Married couple embarks on a long-awaited vacations with the children. They have long planned to spend the holiday together and even agreed with friends, where exactly will rest. The road to the beach was pretty long, but finally they have reached the right place and moved into a rented house. Now nothing can stop them enjoy, forget about all your everyday problems and concerns. They had a great day, but at night it becomes clear to them that quiet time is left behind. The thing is that before their house appeared uninvited guests who are not going to go away until they take away their lives. The strangest thing that they look exactly like they know in advance all their actions. Will the family be saved from themselves?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Horror   Mystery   Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 17:56:04 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Pokémon Detective Pikachu</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1859-pokemon-detective-pikachu.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Action movie occur in the huge metropolis Reim-city, where people live close to Pokemon. Tim is a guy who's dreamt to become a trainer Pokemon. His father Harry is a real legend of the police station, which was the best detective. Man mysteriously disappeared and nobody can find it. Tim really wants to find it, but realizes that most cope with such a complex task will be incredibly difficult. But one night, he encounters a pretty-type Pokémon, Pikachu, who calls himself supersyshhikom. It offers its assistance and the guy claims that they are bound to find Harry.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Adventure    Action    Comedy    Family    Mystery    Sci-Fi]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:48:23 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Maze Runner</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1852-the-maze-runner.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1852-the-maze-runner.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The first part of the plot is based on the eponymous book by James Djeshnera. Once the hero of the paintings sent to lift, not to walk the stairs. As a result, he finds himself in a strange place in the company of 60 teenagers. All they do not remember anything about himself, except for the name. Our hero's name is Thomas. And the place in which he ended up here is called Glejdom. Teens themselves call themselves glejderami. They are in a confined space, the square around which is an impassable maze. The main objective of all the guys-this pass it, because this is the only chance to go back and remember her past.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Action     Mystery     Sci-Fi     Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 16:48:51 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Daphne &amp; Velma</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1838-daphne-amp-velma.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1838-daphne-amp-velma.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[<span>Two girlfriends, future employees of the mysterious organization "Misteri Ink.", try to understand the devilry which is created at their school.</span>]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Action      Comedy      Crime      Horror      Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:25:19 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Spinning Man</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1837-spinning-man.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1837-spinning-man.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Respectable life of professor of philosophy Evan Bertsch begins to fall as details about his unseemly behavior with students appear. In completion to everything the hero becomes the central suspect of case of murder of one of listeners of its course.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Drama       Mystery       Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:22:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Past Malice: An Emma Fielding Mystery</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1833-past-malice-an-emma-fielding-mystery.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1833-past-malice-an-emma-fielding-mystery.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The archeologist Emma Fielding is invited for consultation at sale of the ancient castle which if to trust legegda, was damned. But it is involved in case of murder after the body of other archeologist, her predecessor, was found in the secret room in the cellar of the huge building. Together with the friend, the FBI agent Jim Connor, Fielding it is necessary to pass a way through a set of proofs and to face suspects, each of which could have a reason to wish death to the victim.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Crime        Drama        Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 10:01:05 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Queen of Sin</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1828-the-queen-of-sin.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1828-the-queen-of-sin.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[But once returning, home after work it met the attractive, self-assured businessman Jack who completely changed outlook of the girl. This young man helps to be liberated to the girl, turning her into the person, corrupted and ready for all, for whom there are no barriers and obstacles. However the broken-out torrid love affair with the young businessman as showed further events of the movie, was brought by many troubles and sufferings for nothing to the suspecting heroine ….]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Drama         Mystery         Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:57:25 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Rake</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1814-the-rake.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1814-the-rake.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[There passed twenty years since in the face of juveniles Ben and Ashley the psychopath cruelly killed their parents, and then cut to itself a throat. But the brother with the sister cannot still recover from psychological injuries and from fears that the spiteful spirit which pushed the maniac on murder still lives somewhere nearby.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Horror          Mystery          Thriller]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 12:04:03 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Did I Kill My Mother?</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1808-did-i-kill-my-mother.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1808-did-i-kill-my-mother.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Mother of the girl is found dead a year later after murder of her father which was not solved. The police consider that, perhaps, the daughter committed a crime therefore it and her friends should prove her innocence.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Mystery]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 11:48:18 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>