<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>TV Series - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>TV Series - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>Stranger Things</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1798-stranger-things-season-3-v4.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1798-stranger-things-season-3-v4.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[It is already known that the third season of the television series will be 8 episodes. That is one fewer than in the previous year. The action will take place in the year 1985. This, by the way, there is a very logical explanation Matt Daffera (one of the brothers, creators of the "Stranger Things"): "we can't stay in the year 1984, and cannot so simply travel back on 10 years backward or forward. Children grow very definitely. When will be season 3, they will be plus one year, and it will be noticeable. You know, I even like it. Audience matures, together with our heroes. Viewers will see how children reach adulthood. That's cool! "]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 08:53:07 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Chernobyl</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1854-chernobyl.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1854-chernobyl.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[In the center of the plot-event of the year 1986, when CHERNOBYL NUCLEAR POWER PLANT explodes fourth power unit and a large-scale release of radiation into the atmosphere. The makers claim that the tv series will be told the real story of what happened, which was suppressed in the Soviet Union. On April 25, 1986 CHERNOBYL guide planned stop fourth unit for testing equipment and partial repairs. However, during testing of something going wrong, and night April 26 comes a powerful explosion which completely destroys the reactor. The building in which the unit is partially boned. Starts a large-scale fire on the roof, which spreads to adjacent premises and buildings. The Soviet leadership understands that technological disaster occurred on a global scale, the consequences of which are likely to affect all of humanity. At an emergency meeting in the Kremlin decided to send Soviet scientist-chemist, Valery Legasova, to investigate this terrible incident.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 21:22:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Stranger Things</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1797-stranger-things-season-2-v2.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1797-stranger-things-season-2-v2.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The second season of the show will continue to talk about the adventure of four friends and their families confronted with the consequences of dangerous experiments, the neighbouring lab. After returning from the Twilight World Will started to pursue the horrifying vision. Doctors and psychologists have argued that these are consequences of the shock, but only he could sense the coming of the dark forces. His friends Meanwhile met with attractive age, moved in their humble town with very steep brother. Mike is not in awe of attempts to tighten the team mates another girl, because he never went after the loss of the "eleventh", but the selection does not remain. All other residents of the town continue to engage in routine cases, until the Hopper is seeking a toehold in this dangerous and tries to save them.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 20:59:53 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Stranger Things</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1796-stranger-things-v4.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1796-stranger-things-v4.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The plot revolves around a simple guy named Will. He lives in a small provincial town in the South of the United States, where the locals know each other in person. Once, when will was returning home, he was gone. Naturally, his parents sounded the alarm and tried independently to find a boyfriend, but none of this has happened. Then for the case came from the local sheriff, were all around, but his quest for no avail. Will's best friend Mike till last hoping that guy will find, but then still decided to start its own investigation. Mike soon met with a group of people with superpowers, who told him the whole truth about Uille. S e'togo momenta zhizn Mike changes dramatically, because he now knows too much ...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 20:57:26 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Game of Thrones</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1135-game-of-thrones.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1135-game-of-thrones.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The final eighth season of the series will consist of six episodes. According to unconfirmed information the duration of episodes will be about 1.5 hours. First Issue Date April 14, 2019]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 08:34:55 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>One Punch Man</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1703-one-punch-man.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1703-one-punch-man.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[What have the strongest man in the world? Not so great as it might seem at first glance. When you're just learning to make reached villains literally with one blow, life loses its paint, lost interest in life itself, it's not something to strive for. With this internal crisis faced Saitama-the strongest man on the planet, is stuck in a routine and lost the joy of victories over monsters and criminals. His familiarity with cyborg Genosom opens Saitama new world of superheroes-friends are logged in the superhero Association on behalf of Justice to fight evil, but the strongest one in the world still boring ...]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 18:21:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Bad Seed</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1702-the-bad-seed.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1702-the-bad-seed.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The focus of the plot turns out to be a story of two brothers who grew up in the rich and prosperous family. Their lives are always hanging on by a thread, but additional constraints creates new tragedy in the neighbouring House. A woman who lived nearby, was found murdered, so the main characters now seeks attention. They must also begin to understand what happened, because no one knows what is really going on around. The truth is, events soon changed with stunning speed, after all, begins a crucial campaign that can change the life of the whole city. Journalists trying to get new information, and the death of a woman turns out to be pripletena to the upcoming elections. Suddenly it becomes clear that even the investigator responsible for the disclosure of crimes, have their own interests in this matter. But how is it connected? How does killing innocent person can benefit anyone on the campaign?]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 11:37:49 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Supernatural</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1382-supernatural-season-14.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1382-supernatural-season-14.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Michael travels the world in the body of Dean Winchester, asking people one urgent question, but no one can give the answer that would satisfy the archangel. On the path of Michael appears the healer Joe, who once helped Lucifer rule in heaven.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 17:59:42 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Supernatural</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1379-supernatural-season-13.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1379-supernatural-season-13.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Storyline picture is revealed in the history of the two brothers Winchesters that fight dark forces and guests from another world for the benefit of mankind. Originally the motive to seek evil forces served as revenge. Mother in childhood heroes was lost from the hands of one of these "uninvited guests". In the coming time, the brothers begin to look at the situation more globally. Now they are driven by people, the salvation of mankind.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 17:54:54 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Supernatural</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1378-supernatural-season-12.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/tvseries/1378-supernatural-season-12.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Now in the universe a complete mess. Unknown anything concrete. Darkness was sealed or not, where is God. All these questions were only questions. After the events of all these huge changes, it becomes clear that the world now would not be the same. Key heroes now divided. Everyone thinks that Dean died, was destroyed by a bomb from a shower.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[TV Series]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 17:51:58 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>