<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Western - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Western - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>The Timber</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1669-the-timber.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1669-the-timber.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Year 1889. In ice Alaska, during a gold-rush, brothers Samuel and Wyatt go to a dangerous travel. To keep honor of the house, they have to find the tiranichny father who many years ago left them. Ahead they have a heap of troubles with cruel bandits. Gloomy scenes and crude climate grow dim before greed, thirst of the power and death which they face.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Drama  Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 20:51:02 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Diablo</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1634-diablo.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1634-diablo.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Western about the young veteran with "post-military" stressful frustration. Having gone on a trace of the kidnapped wife, it faces again those horrors which experienced at the front.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Adventure   Action   Thriller   Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 19:40:38 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Forsaken</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1597-forsaken.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1597-forsaken.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The hitman John Henry leaves the bloody craft and comes back to the hometown, hoping to restore the relations with own father.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Action    Drama    Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 19:23:31 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Slow West</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1530-slow-west.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1530-slow-west.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[History of the adventurer by the name of Silas accompanying on a dangerous travel along all American border of the 16-year-old fellow by the name of Jay Cavendish. Jay searches for the girl with whom he is in love. <br><br>They were crossed accidentally, the lonely wolf who became separated from pack of wolves and the hare who appeared in a wolf den. He could allow it to die, could kill, but did not seize a throat, and went with it on a trace, helping to find the love which hid somewhere, seeing off through fields of hatred and the wood of fear, firmly, without having decided what to do next with it and with itself.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies     Adventure     Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 19:48:48 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Jane Got a Gun</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1477-jane-got-a-gun.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1477-jane-got-a-gun.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[McCann's bandits pursue Ham who tried to beat off gang. Honeycombed by bullets, he takes cover on the ranch of the beauty wife Jane. She should address for protection the one whom she would like to see least of all — to the former lover. Jane needs to forget the past, to master feelings and to become strong and uncompromising to save family from punishment of gang of mercenaries.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies      Action      Drama      Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:01:03 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Ridiculous 6</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1199-the-ridiculous-6.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1199-the-ridiculous-6.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The comedy western will tell story of the man who remained in the early childhood the orphan and grew up in the tribe of Indians Apaches who brought up it and learned in the traditions and laws. The main character known as "White Knife" — the criminal who unexpectedly detects that not one on light: it has five stepbrothers. Having united, they make the decision to find their father who got lost somewhere on open spaces of the Wild West. Here also the real adventures which so fascinating, are how comical begin.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies       Comedy       Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 08:40:13 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bone Tomahawk</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1179-bone-tomahawk.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1179-bone-tomahawk.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Four men go to the remote lands of the Wild West to save group of prisoners of caves of cannibals.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies        Adventure        Drama        Horror        Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:27:34 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Revenant</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1177-the-revenant.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1177-the-revenant.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The hunter Hugh Glass is seriously wounded on novel open spaces of the American Wild West. Companion Hugh on group of subjugators of new lands John Fitszherald foully leaves it to die alone. Now Glass had only one weapon — his will power. He is ready to throw down a challenge to the primitive nature, severe winter and hostile tribes of Indians, only to survive and revenge Fitszherald.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies         Adventure         Action         Biography         Drama         Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 16:21:16 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Hateful Eight</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/1173-the-hateful-eight.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/1173-the-hateful-eight.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The USA after Civil war. The legendary headhunter Joe Root by nickname Veshatel escorts concluded. On the way to them some more travelers are beaten. The blizzard forces the company to look for the shelter in a bench detached where very motley society was already located: general of confederates, Mexican, cowboy … And one of them — not that for whom gives itself.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies          Crime          Drama          Mystery          Thriller          Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 16:11:43 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Hell or High Water</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/976-hell-or-high-water.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/976-hell-or-high-water.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The young guy Toby and his elder brother Tanner who recently went out of prison learn that the huge credit hung on their died mother. And now, if not to repay the debt in a certain time, the bank will appropriate the family ranch. Trying to find the necessary sum in so short time, Toby persuades the brother to take incredibly risky step – to rob several small banks. Having armed and having put on mask faces, brothers go to a dangerous tour on local financial institutions, without suspecting at all where this mad idea can bring them.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies           Action           Crime           Drama           Thriller           Western]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 09:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>