<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Coming Soon - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</title>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/</link>
<language>ru</language>
<description>Coming Soon - FlixGo - Watch Free Movies Online In Full HD</description>
<generator>DataLife Engine</generator><item>
<title>The Nut Job 2: Nutty by Nature</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/649-the-nut-job-2-nutty-by-nature.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/649-the-nut-job-2-nutty-by-nature.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Throughout cheerful adventures having a tail the squirrel the Ill-natured person and to his friends needs to act together again. This time — to save the house: the mayor conceived to cut down their park and to construct heartless attractions on its place … Fortunately, at the Ill-natured person and other fans of peanut there is a plan in which not the last part is assigned to new friends of our heroes — white mice under leadership of wise Mr. Fenga.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies  Adventure  Action  Animation  Family  Fantasy  Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 19:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bring It On: Worldwide #Cheersmack</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/549-bring-it-on-worldwide-cheersmack-v3.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/549-bring-it-on-worldwide-cheersmack-v3.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[To young Destinee, the captain of three-time champions fans of "Rebells", the mysterious Truth team throws down a serious challenge. Preparation for a global Internet competition takes place hardly, problems appear one by one. To win, Destinee should be pacified the ego and to understand that the true friendship means to her.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies   Romance   Sport   Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 20:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>The Good Catholic</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/movies/526-the-good-catholic.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/movies/526-the-good-catholic.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Most of all in life Daniel loved the work of the priest in the small town. And then met Jane. Yes it will be helped by the Lord.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Movies    Drama    Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 20:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Papillon</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/171-papillon.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/171-papillon.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Sweet Katie Price has just turned seventeen, but ever since her childhood she has to stay cooped up indoors with tinted windows. The fact of the matter is that Katie has a rare genetic disease, a melanosis. It is progressing speedily and the girl can not go outdoors during the day for the sun rays would instantly destroy her skin, which will be fatal for her. Forced to live in an ivory tower, day by day she composes beautiful songs to a guitar that few will ever hear. Katie communicates only with her father and childhood friend Morgan.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:38:46 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>London Fields</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/170-london-fields.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/170-london-fields.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The beautiful Nicola is a charming woman who always gets what she wants, but she has a gift that is far above a pretty face for she is a seer. But a gift turns into a curse for her. More than once in her sleep Nikola sees her death, and it seems that the murderer will soon come for her to make the horror come true. Nichola can never see the murderer's face which troubles her even more.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:38:05 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>A Simple Favor</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/167-a-simple-favor.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/167-a-simple-favor.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[Stephanie is a lone mom, who brings up her little preschooler son in the Connecticut suburbs. Her husband died a sudden death right after the child was born and now she has a tough time. One simple request suddenly rocks her world forever. Her only distraction has always been Web-chatting with other moms like her. The girl was making daily posts in her blog about the problems of motherhood while her life was going on rather monotonously and uneventfully, up until that one day when a glamorous neighbor knocked at her house door with a request to pick up her son after school.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:36:01 +0100</pubDate>
</item><item>
<title>Bel Canto</title>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/166-bel-canto.html</guid>
<link>https://flixgo.cc/coming-soon/166-bel-canto.html</link>
<description><![CDATA[The screen adaptation of a thrill-a-minute bestseller by Anne Patchett. Thestory is set in South America. A worldwide renowned opera singer Roxanne Coss gets an alluring proposal to perform at the birthday party of a leading Japanese businessman Katsumi Hosokawa. A merry gathering of celebrities, businessmen and politicians has come to the manor of a birthday celebrant, who is well known for his passion for opera. No sooner than Roxana finishes her last song, some unbidden guests step into the living room. And the newcomers are none other than a group of terrorist revolters. Criminals demand a chat with the president of the country, but as it happened Mr. President had chosen not to come to the party but to stay at home instead and watch his favorite TV series. So the revolters take all those present, including Roxane Coss, as their hostages and demand that the government release prisoners of conscience.]]></description>
<category><![CDATA[Coming Soon]]></category>
<dc:creator>Admin</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:35:12 +0100</pubDate>
</item></channel></rss>